orhp.com 2018-08-30

# Privacy Policy | Old Republic Home Protection

## To Our Customers

Maintaining your privacy is important to us, so whether you visit our web sites or contact our service center, please be assured that we are keeping your personal information safe and secure. We actively take steps to keep unauthorized persons from seeing, stealing, or using your personal information.

## Information We Collect

We collect and maintain personal information from you to better serve you and to administer services on your behalf.

We collect non-public personal information about you from the following sources:

  * Information we receive on home warranty applications and other forms,
  * Information we receive in regard to your transactions with us.

Items of personal information that we may collect from you are name, property address, mailing address, telephone number, credit card number, and email address. We do not collect social security numbers, date/place of birth, maiden names, biometric/genetic data, or driver license information, nor do we track persons who contact our website. Information Disclosure and Sharing:

We do not disclose any personal information about our customers, or former customers, to anyone, except as required by law. We do not sell your personal information to any outside party. We may share your personal information with business partners for the performance of services. Business partners may include service providers who provide service to you under the terms and conditions of the Home Warranty Plan Contract, data processing companies that help us administer services to you, or companies that might otherwise assist us in fulfilling our obligations to you. These companies and service providers are subject to confidentiality provisions and restrictions that prohibit them from using the information beyond the performance of the specified services on your behalf, and are specifically prohibited from independent use of the information.

## Information Protection

We restrict access to your personal information to only authorized individuals who need to know the information in order to provide products and services to you. We also maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to further protect your personal information.

## Data Breach

If an unauthorized person has (or it seems likely they have) seen, stolen, or used your personal information, a data breach has occurred. We will notify you in the event of a data breach. This notice will:

    * Be sent in writing by first-class mail or by email, if you have agreed to that,
    * Be sent soon after a data breach, and never more than sixty (60) days after a breach is discovered,
    * Describe the type of information involved in the data breach, and the steps you can take to protect yourself from identity theft or fraud,
    * Describe the actions we and our business partners have taken to keep your personal information safe,
    * Include contact information for the three nationwide credit bureaus,
    * Include contact information for all parties involved in the breach.
    * In the event of a data breach, you will receive one (1) year of identity theft protection at no cost to you.

## Rights & Choices

You can view your personal information online or within documents you receive from us. If your information needs to be changed/corrected, you may do so online or call us at [1.800.445.6999](tel:8004456999).
